Guide to the Yale College Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Horace Taft as dean, 1963-1979; Accession 1984-A-030
  - Subject File, Series I
    - Restricted
      - Salaries, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 792)
      - Visiting Faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 793)
  - Correspondence, Minutes and Memoranda
    - A general, 1967-1972 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Academic Obligations of Athletics, Committee on (Mr. Buxton), 1969 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Data Services
      - Automated Student Record Keeping System - Proposed, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 3 - 5)
      - Computer Systems, Yale College, 1974-1977 (Box 55, Folder 6 - 7)
      - Course Master Analysis, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Course Master File -- Users' Guide, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Course and Grade Systems overview, Yale College Study, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Student Data Base Reference Manual, undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Taft Committee on Automated Student Record Keeping, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Master Course List, 1972-1973 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Advertising, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Affirmative Action Search Questionnaire: Term Appointments, 1971-1973 (Box 58, Folder 15 - 16)
    - Alterations, 1976-1978 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Appointment, Term -- Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Appointments, Junior and Term, 1965-1969 (Box 58, Folder 19 - 20)
    - Attendance Records -- Administrative Office, 1976-1977 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Bills, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Biological Sciences, Senior Appointments, 1965-1969 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Bursar, 1975-1978 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - C general, 1967-1972 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - College Seminar Program, Report of the Sub-Committee to Review the, undated (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - Combined B.A.-M.A. Program, undated (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - Committees, Yale College: Joint Committees and Standing Committees, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - Communications Department, 1974-1979 (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - Corporation Votes, 1970-1972 (Box 59, Folder 31 - 33)
    - Correspondence, general, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence re: Faculty Meetings, 1965-1972 (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Council on Priorities and Planning: Report, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Course of Study Committee: miscellaneous correspondence and memoranda, 1965-1966 (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Course of Study
      - Distribution Guidelines -- Letters on Proposed, 1965-1966 (Box 59, Folder 38)
      - Distribution Guidelines, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 39 - 40)
      - Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 41)
      - Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - Deans, Assistant -- Yale College: Payroll, 1974-1976 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - Deans, College: Payroll, 1968-1972 (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Dean's Office, Yale College: Salary Information, 1946-1972 (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Deeds of Gifts, 1963-1967 (Box 60, Folder 46)
    - Directed Studies, 1968-1969 (Box 60, Folder 47)
    - Directors of Undergraduate Studies, Committee on, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 48)
    - Divisional Majors (Statements), 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 49)
    - Drama, 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 50)
    - E general, 1969-1972 (Box 60, Folder 51)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty Accounts, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 52)
    - Effectiveness of the Guideline System, Report on, undated (Box 60, Folder 53)
    - Entertainment Expenses, 1975-1979 (Box 60, Folder 54)
    - Ethiopia, Archeological, undated (Box 60, Folder 55)
    - Faculty, General: Yale College, 1966-1970 (Box 60, Folder 56 - 59)
    - Faculty, General: Yale College, 1970-1972 (Box 61, Folder 60 - 62)
    - Faculty Lists, 1963-1964 (Box 61, Folder 63)
    - Faculty Lists, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 64)
    - Faculty Lists, Departmental, 1973-1975 (Box 61, Folder 65 - 66)
    - Faculty Lists and Worksheets, Yale College, 1945-1972 (Box 61, Folder 67 - 68)
    - Faculty Lists and Worksheets, Yale College, 1972-1974 (Box 62, Folder 69 - 70)
    - Faculty Meetings, Yale College, 1970-1973 (Box 62, Folder 71 - 75)
    - Attendance, 1972-1973 (Box 62, Folder 76)
    - Attendance, 1972-1973 (Box 63, Folder 77)
    - Faculty Meetings, Yale College, 1973-1975 (Box 63, Folder 78 - 83)
    - Forms Miscellaneous, 1969, undated (Box 63, Folder 84 - 85)
    - The Future of the College and the Graduate School, Report of the Committee on, undated (Box 64, Folder 86)
    - G general, 1967-1972 (Box 64, Folder 87)
    - Graduate School Appointments, 1966-1972 (Box 64, Folder 88)
    - H general, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 89)
    - Humanities: Senior Appointments, 1965-1969 (Box 64, Folder 90)
    - Humanities: Tenure Appointments, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 91)
    - Institutional Research, Office of: Yale College Spring and Fall Term Grades, 1970-1971 (Box 64, Folder 92)
    - Joint Board of Permanent Officers, Yale College and Graduate School
      - 1959-1969 (Box 64, Folder 93 - 97)
      - 1970-1976 (Box 65, Folder 98 - 107)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 66, Folder 108 - 110)
    - Joint Committees and Faculty List, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 111)
    - Junior and Term Appointments, Committee on, 1969-1972 (Box 66, Folder 112)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1969-1972 (Box 66, Folder 113 - 116)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1971-1974 (Box 67, Folder 117 - 119)
    - Letters, Forms, etc. -- mailed: Copies of, 1967-1972 (Box 67, Folder 120)
    - Major Appointments Committee: minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 67, Folder 122)
    - Morse Fellowship Applicants, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 128)
    - N general, 1968-1969 (Box 68, Folder 129)
    - P general, 1967-1972 (Box 68, Folder 130)
    - Permanent Officers, undated (Box 68, Folder 131)
    - Personnel/Union, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 132)
    - Potential Faculty Resolutions Pertaining to the Report of the Study Group on Yale College, Draft of, undated (Box 68, Folder 133)
    - Provost, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 134)
    - R general, undated (Box 68, Folder 135)
    - Registration and Grade Recording, Committee on, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 136)
    - Residential College System, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 137)
    - Rodgers, John -- Chairman of Joint Board of Permanent Officers, undated (Box 68, Folder 138)
    - S general, 1969-1971 (Box 68, Folder 139)
    - Sciences, Combined -- Expenses, 1975-1978 (Box 68, Folder 140)
    - Secretary's Office, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 141)
    - Security, University Committee on, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 142)
    - Senior Appointments -- Physical Sciences, 1965-1969 (Box 68, Folder 143)
    - Senior Appointments Committees, 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 144)
    - Senior Appointments -- Social Sciences, 1965-1969 (Box 68, Folder 145)
    - Social Sciences -- Tenure Appointments, 1964-1965 (Box 69, Folder 146)
    - Source Code -- YCSR Data Base Management, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 147)
    - Steering Committee, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 148)
    - Strike, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 149)
    - Student Evaluations, 1965-1970 (Box 69, Folder 150)
    - Study Commission on Governance -- Final Report, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 151)
    - Summer Academic Programs and Conferences, University Committee on, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 152)
    - Summer Programs, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 153)
    - The Student-Teacher Relationship: Tape made Feb 1972 based on student and faculty discussion groups. Special Project of the Yale College Committee on Teaching and Learning (Box 69, Folder 154)
    - Tape No. 1: Young, Jeff, 22 February 1972 (Box 70, Folder 155)
    - Tape No. 2: Young, Jeff, 22 February 1972 (Box 70, Folder 156)
    - Tape: Young, Jeff, undated (Box 70, Folder 157)
    - Tape, undated (Box 70, Folder 158)
    - Teacher Training Program, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 159)
    - Teaching Assistants, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 160)
    - Teaching and Learning, Committee on, 1967-1973 (Box 71, Folder 161 - 167)
    - Telephone Accounts, 1975-1976 (Box 71, Folder 168)
    - Travel Expense Reports, 1975-1979 (Box 71, Folder 169)
    - Wasserman, Harry, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 171)
    - Restricted
      - Payroll, casual, 1975-1979 (Box 72, Folder 172)
      - Personnel, 1974-1979 (Box 72, Folder 173)
      - Personnel Profiles, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 174)
      - Personnel Profile Forms: miscellaneous, 1974-1977 (Box 72, Folder 175 - 176)
      - Secretaries, College Deans', 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder 177)
      - Student Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 72, Folder 178 - 179)
      - Student Letters re Faculty, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 180)
  - Financial Records -- Budget Sheets
    - Administrative Offices: Schools and Departments, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 1 - 4)
    - Divisional Majors, Discussion Groups, Directed Studies, Early Concentration Program
      - 1967-1968 (Box 74, Folder 6 - 7)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Divisional Majors, Discussion Groups, Early Concentration Program, 1969-1971 (Box 74, Folder 9 - 10)
    - "Profiles of Yale College" -- Surveys Conducted for the Study Group of Yale College, undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Administrative Offices: Schools and Departments, 1967-1968 (Box 75, Folder 12 - 14)
    - College Deans, 1967-1970 (Box 75, Folder 15 - 17)
    - Colleges: Budget Worksheets, 1969-1970 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Discussion Groups, 1968-1969 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Directed Studies, 1968-1970 (Box 75, Folder 20 - 21)
    - Divisional Majors, 1968-1970 (Box 75, Folder 22 - 23)
    - Early Concentration Program, 1968-1970 (Box 75, Folder 24 - 25)
    - Mellon Funds, 1965-1968 (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Scholars of the House, 1968-1970 (Box 76, Folder 27 - 28)
    - Blank Forms, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 76, Folder 29 - 30)
  - Graduate Student Appointments
    - 1969-1970
      - Administrative Science (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - American Studies (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Anthropology (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Astronomy (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Biology (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Chemistry (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Classics (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Economics (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Engineering and Applied Science (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - English (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Geology (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - German (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - History (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - History of Art (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Martz Committee Appointments (Box 77, Folder 15)
      - Mathematics (Box 77, Folder 16)
      - Molecular Biophysics (Box 77, Folder 17)
      - Music (Box 77, Folder 18)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 77, Folder 19)
      - Peabody Museum (Box 77, Folder 20)
      - Philosophy (Box 77, Folder 21)
      - Physics (Box 77, Folder 22)
      - Political Science (Box 77, Folder 23)
      - Psychology (Box 77, Folder 24)
      - Religious Studies (Box 77, Folder 25)
      - Romance Languages (Box 77, Folder 26)
      - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 77, Folder 27)
      - Sociology (Box 77, Folder 28)
      - Statistics (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - 1970-1971
      - Administrative Sciences (Box 77, Folder 30)
      - Afro-American Studies (Box 77, Folder 31)
      - American Studies (Box 77, Folder 32)
      - Anthropology (Box 77, Folder 33)
      - Astronomy (Box 77, Folder 34)
      - Biology (Box 77, Folder 35)
      - Chemistry (Box 77, Folder 36)
      - Classics (Box 78, Folder 37)
      - Computer Science (Box 78, Folder 38)
      - Economics (Box 78, Folder 39)
      - Engineering and Applied Science (Box 78, Folder 40)
      - English (Box 78, Folder 41)
      - Geology and Geophysics (Box 78, Folder 42)
      - German (Box 78, Folder 43)
      - History (Box 78, Folder 44)
      - History of Art (Box 78, Folder 45)
      - Linguistics (Box 78, Folder 46)
      - Mathematics (Box 78, Folder 47)
      - Martz Committee (Box 78, Folder 48)
      - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry (Box 78, Folder 49)
      - Music (Box 78, Folder 50)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 78, Folder 51)
      - Peabody Museum (Box 78, Folder 52)
      - Philosophy (Box 78, Folder 53)
      - Physics (Box 78, Folder 54)
      - Political Science (Box 78, Folder 55)
      - Psychology (Box 78, Folder 56)
      - Religious Studies (Box 78, Folder 57)
      - Romance Languages (Box 78, Folder 58)
      - Sociology (Box 78, Folder 59)
      - Statistics (Box 78, Folder 60)
    - 1971-1972
      - Administrative Sciences (Box 78, Folder 61)
      - Afro-American Studies (Box 78, Folder 62)
      - American Studies (Box 78, Folder 63)
      - Anthropology (Box 78, Folder 64)
      - Astronomy (Box 78, Folder 65)
      - Biology (Box 78, Folder 66)
      - Chemistry (Box 78, Folder 67)
      - Classics (Box 78, Folder 68)
      - Computer Science (Box 78, Folder 69)
      - Drama (Box 78, Folder 70)
      - Economics (Box 78, Folder 71)
      - Engineering and Applied Science (Box 79, Folder 72)
      - English (Box 79, Folder 73)
      - Geology and Geophysics (Box 79, Folder 74)
      - German (Box 79, Folder 75)
      - History (Box 79, Folder 76)
      - History of Art (Box 79, Folder 77)
      - Linguistics (Box 79, Folder 78)
      - Mathematics (Box 79, Folder 79)
      - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry (Box 79, Folder 80)
      - Music (Box 79, Folder 81)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 79, Folder 82)
      - Peabody Museum (Box 79, Folder 83)
      - Philosophy (Box 79, Folder 84)
      - Physics (Box 79, Folder 85)
      - Political Science (Box 79, Folder 86)
      - Psychology (Box 79, Folder 87)
      - Residential College Seminars (Box 79, Folder 88)
      - Romance Languages (Box 79, Folder 89)
      - Religious Studies (Box 79, Folder 90)
      - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 79, Folder 91)
      - Sociology (Box 79, Folder 92)
      - Statistics (Box 79, Folder 93)
    - 1972-1973
      - Administrative Sciences (Box 80, Folder 94)
      - American Studies (Box 80, Folder 95)
      - Anthropology (Box 80, Folder 96)
      - Astronomy (Box 80, Folder 97)
      - Biology (Box 80, Folder 98)
      - Chemistry (Box 80, Folder 99)
      - Classics (Box 80, Folder 100)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 80, Folder 101)
      - Computer Science (Box 80, Folder 102)
      - Drama (Box 80, Folder 103)
      - Economics (Box 80, Folder 104)
      - Engineering and Applied Science (Box 80, Folder 105)
      - English (Box 80, Folder 106)
      - Forestry (Box 80, Folder 107)
      - Geology and Geophysics (Box 80, Folder 108)
      - German (Box 80, Folder 109)
      - History (Box 80, Folder 110)
      - History of Art (Box 80, Folder 111)
      - Linguistics (Box 80, Folder 112)
      - Mathematics (Box 80, Folder 113)
      - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry (Box 80, Folder 114)
      - Music (Box 80, Folder 115)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 80, Folder 116)
      - Peabody Museum (Box 80, Folder 117)
      - Philosophy (Box 80, Folder 118)
      - Physics (Box 81, Folder 119)
      - Political Science (Box 81, Folder 120)
      - Psychology (Box 81, Folder 121)
      - Religious Studies (Box 81, Folder 122)
      - Residential College Seminars (Box 81, Folder 123)
      - Romance Languages (Box 81, Folder 124)
      - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 81, Folder 125)
      - Sociology (Box 81, Folder 126)
- Records of Horace Taft as dean, 1965-1980; Accession 1985-A-014
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2016
  - 1963-1980
    - Accreditation (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
    - Administrative Science Major (Box 1, Folder 3 - 5)
    - Administrative Science Proposal (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Sciences (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Admissions Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Admissions Undergraduate (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Advanced Placement (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 1, Folder 11 - 14)
    - African, Research Southern (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - African Studies (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Afro-American Studies (Box 1, Folder 18 - 20)
    - Alterations (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Alumni (Box 2, Folder 22 - 25)
    - Alumni Journal (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Alumni Magazine (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - American Association for Higher Education (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - American Council on Education (Box 2, Folder 30 - 32)
    - American Studies (Box 2, Folder 33 - 34)
    - Anthropology (Box 2, Folder 35 - 36)
    - Applied Mathematics (Box 2, Folder 37 - 38)
    - Appointment Procedures (Box 3, Folder 39 - 41)
    - Appointments, Senior (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Archeology (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Architecture (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Arts and Yale College (Box 3, Folder 45 - 47)
    - Arts School and Art Major (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Asian American Studies (Box 3, Folder 49 - 50)
    - Association of Colleges in New England (Box 3, Folder 51 - 52)
    - Association of American Colleges (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Astronomy (Box 3, Folder 54 - 55)
    - Athletics (Box 4, Folder 56 - 57)
    - Attendance (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Audio Visual (Box 4, Folder 59 - 60)
    - Auditing (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Bachelor of Arts/Masters Combined (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Band (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Beinecke Plaza Affair (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Biology (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Black Students at Yale (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Blue Alert (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - British Art Center (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - British Studies (Box 4, Folder 69 - 70)
    - Budget Committee (Box 4, Folder 71 - 74)
    - Budget Committee Decisions (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Budget Committee of the Arts and Sciences (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Bursar (Box 4, Folder 77 - 78)
    - Business (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Calendar (Box 4, Folder 80 - 81)
    - Campaign for Yale (Box 5, Folder 82 - 84)
    - Campus (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Campus Police (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Canadian Studies (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Career Advisory and Placement (Box 5, Folder 88 - 90)
    - Chairmen (Box 5, Folder 91 - 92)
    - Chaplains (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Charities Drive (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Classics (Box 5, Folder 95 - 96)
    - Classroom (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - College Board (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - College Bowl (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - College Council (Box 5, Folder 100 - 101)
    - College Seminar Alternatives (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Combined Science Major (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Combined Sciences (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Committees -- Standard and Special (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Committees -- Yale College (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Communications and Information, University (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Comparative Literature (Box 6, Folder 108 - 109)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Comptroller's office (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Computer Science (Box 6, Folder 112 - 113)
    - Computing at Yale (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Concilium (Box 6, Folder 115 - 116)
    - Conferences, Student (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE) (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Consulting (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Corporation Actions (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Council on Comparative Study of Culture and Society (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Course Critique (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Credit Base (Box 6, Folder 123 - 124)
    - Credit/Fail (Box 6, Folder 125 - 126)
    - Custodial Services (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Davenport (Box 7, Folder 129 - 130)
    - Dean's Annual Report (Box 7, Folder 131 - 132)
    - Deans, College (Box 7, Folder 133 - 134)
    - Deans, College Candidates (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Deans' Conference (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Dean's Conferences (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Deanship Search (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - Dean's Office Budget (Box 7, Folder 139 - 140)
    - Dean's Office Staff (Box 7, Folder 141 - 142)
    - Deans of Schools (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Devane Fellowship (Box 8, Folder 144 - 145)
    - Director of Undergraduate Studies (Box 8, Folder 146 - 147)
    - Directory, University (Box 8, Folder 148 - 149)
    - Distributional Guidelines (Box 8, Folder 150 - 153)
    - Divisions of Advisors-Faculty (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - Dramat (Box 8, Folder 155 - 156)
    - Drugs (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - Dublin, University of (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - East Asian Languages and Literatures (Box 8, Folder 159 - 160)
    - Economic History (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Economics (Box 9, Folder 162 - 163)
    - Economics and Political Science Major (Box 9, Folder 164)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty (Box 9, Folder 165 - 169)
    - Editor (Box 9, Folder 170)
    - Editor, Yale College (Box 10, Folder 171)
    - Education in the College (Box 10, Folder 172 - 174)
    - Energy (Box 10, Folder 175)
    - English (Box 10, Folder 176 - 177)
    - Enrollment (Box 10, Folder 178)
    - Enrollment and Majors (Box 10, Folder 179)
    - Examinations (Box 10, Folder 180)
    - Faculty Advising (Box 10, Folder 181)
    - Faculty Handbook (Box 10, Folder 182)
    - Faculty Problems (Box 11, Folder 183 - 184)
    - Faculty Review Procedure (Box 11, Folder 185 - 187)
    - Faculty Rights and Privacy (Box 11, Folder 188)
    - Faculty of Yale College (Box 11, Folder 189 - 191)
    - Fellowships (Box 11, Folder 192 - 193)
    - Fence Club (Box 11, Folder 194)
    - Film (Box 11, Folder 195)
    - Film Committee (Box 11, Folder 196)
    - Financial Aid (Box 12, Folder 197 - 198)
    - Fire Safety (Box 12, Folder 199)
    - Five-Year Bachelor-of-the-Arts Degree (Box 12, Folder 200 - 201)
    - Flaherty Study Center (Box 12, Folder 202)
    - Foreign Languages (Box 12, Folder 203 - 204)
    - Foreign Students (Box 12, Folder 205)
    - Forestry School (Box 12, Folder 206)
    - Freshmen (Box 12, Folder 207 - 208)
    - Freshman Counselors (Box 12, Folder 209)
    - Freshman Handbook (Box 12, Folder 210)
    - Gaudon Subcommittee (Box 12, Folder 211)
    - Giamatti (Box 12, Folder 212 - 213)
    - Gilbert and Sullivan Society (Box 12, Folder 214)
    - Girnbel Cup (Box 12, Folder 215 - 216)
    - Goldstein (Box 12, Folder 217)
    - Golf Course (Box 12, Folder 218)
    - Graduate Record Examinations Board (Box 12, Folder 219)
    - Graduate School (Box 12, Folder 220 - 221)
    - Guggenheim (Box 12, Folder 222)
    - Gymnasiurn (Box 12, Folder 223)
    - Handicapped (Box 13, Folder 224 - 225)
    - Health Service (Box 13, Folder 226 - 227)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 13, Folder 228)
    - History of Science and Medicine (Box 13, Folder 229 - 230)
    - Honors and Special Projects Committee (Box 13, Folder 231 - 232)
    - Housing (Box 13, Folder 233)
    - Human Subjects (Box 13, Folder 234)
    - Humanities (Box 13, Folder 235)
    - Humanities Council, Connecticut (Box 13, Folder 236)
    - Humanities, National Endowment for the (Box 13, Folder 237 - 238)
    - Humanities, Special Courses in the (Box 13, Folder 239 - 240)
    - Inauguration (Box 13, Folder 241)
    - Industrial Relations (Box 13, Folder 242)
    - Industry Relations, Business (Box 13, Folder 243)
    - Inter-Office Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 244)
    - Internship Program (Box 14, Folder 245 - 248)
    - Invitations (Box 14, Folder 249 - 250)
    - Job Opportunities (Box 14, Folder 251 - 254)
    - Junior Committee on Combined BA/MS (Box 14, Folder 255)
    - Junior Sciences and Humanities Symposium (Box 14, Folder 256)
    - Junior Year Abroad (Box 14, Folder 257)
    - Keys (Box 15, Folder 258)
    - Late Work, Committee (Box 15, Folder 259)
    - Latin American Studies (Box 15, Folder 260)
    - Latino (Box 15, Folder 261)
    - Leaves of Absence -- College Deans (Box 15, Folder 262)
    - Leaves of Absence -- Students (Box 15, Folder 263)
    - Lectureships (Box 15, Folder 264)
    - Legal Advisor (Box 15, Folder 265)
    - Legal Matters (Box 15, Folder 266)
    - Legal Studies (Box 15, Folder 267)
    - Library (Box 15, Folder 268 - 269)
    - Lilly Endowment (Box 15, Folder 270)